

CONTACT ME

- +38 (093) 916-16-98
- 0969125133k@gmail.com
- GitHub
- <u>Linkedin</u>
- Telegram

SUMMARY

I am goal-oriented and result-oriented. I consider difficult tasks a challenge and always find a way to solve them. I have career growth experience. The following help me in my work: high work capacity, the ability to learn quickly,

and stress resistance. I appreciate the opportunity to gain new knowledge and professional development in my work.

TECH SKILLS

- HTML5/CSS3
- JavaScript
- React Redux
- Styled-components, Material UI
- REST API
- Parcel, Webpack, Node.js
- GIT
- MongoDB
- Postman

SOFT SKILLS

- Ability to work efficiently both individually and in a team Critica
- thinking skills
- Decision making skills
- Quick learning skills

LANGUAGES

- English intermediate
- Ukrainian native

Inna Kukla

JUNIOR

PROJECT EXPERIENCE

WebStudio, Link

[HTML, SASS, JS]

A website of WebStudio company. Responsive design, transform effects, modal windows. Role: developer. Individual project.

Filmoteka, Link

[HTML, SASS, JS, Handlebars, REST API, AJAX, Parcel]

Site, which is connected to the TMDB database with the ability to navigate popular films search for a film and add it to the list.

Role: developer. Command project.

YourPet, Link

[JavaScript, React (Hooks, Routers, Redux, Redux Toolkit), MongoDB, REST API]

Site, where you can find, sell and give in good hands pats. You can register, log in, add, remove or filter pats and log out. You can save and delete information about your own pats. Also, you can read last news. Role: developer. Command project.

Mobile Application, Link [React Native]

It's mobile application, where you can make foto with location and post it. And you can watch posts other people and leave comments.

Role: developer. Individual project.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Front-End Developer

Anomi | Dec 2023 - present

• Development of a back office for a mobile application

General Manager

"Portum" club | Aug 2021 - present

Ensuring conditions for uninterrupted operation of the club

EDUCATIONAL HISTORY

IT School GoIT

Fullstack Developer | 2021 - 2023

Vadym Hetman Kyiv National Economic University

Economics, Master Degree in Personnel
Management and Labour Economics | 2016 - 2019